Guide to the Peter Salovey, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the president, 2012-2018; Accession 2019-A-0015
  - Other Universities
    - National Tsing Hua University Honorary Degree Ceremony, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - National University of Singapore Insurance and Liability, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - National University of Singapre Address, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - New Mexico Highlands University Correspondence, 0 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - New York State University at Buffalo Correspondence, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Northern Kentucky University Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Norwegian University of Science and Technology Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Ontario University Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - O.P. Jindal Global University Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - University of Oregon Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - University of Oregon Self-Study, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - Peer University Organizational Chart, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Peking University Academic Freedom, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Peking University Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Peking University Day at Yale, 2013 September 24 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - Peking University Xia Yeliang Issue, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - University of Pennsylvania Correspondence, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - Pratt Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - Rensselaer Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - Rice University Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - University of Rochester Correspondence, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Rutgers University Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - College of Saint Benedict Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - Universidad de Jao Danlo Delegation, 2013 october 25 (Box 22, Folder 72)
    - University of San Paolo Yale Psychiatry Exchange Program, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Seattle University Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - Sewanee University Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - Shandong Yingcai University Correspondence, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - Shangai Jiao Tong University Collaborations, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - Shangai Jiao Tong University Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - Shangai Jiao Tong University Delegation, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 79)
    - Shanghai Jiao Tong Universith Salovey Honorary Degree, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 80)
    - Shanghai Tech University Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 81)
    - Shanghai Tech University Visit Materials, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 82)
    - Smith College Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 22, Folder 83)
    - Smith College Inauguration of McCartney, 2013 October 19 (Box 22, Folder 84)
    - Sophia University Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 85)
    - University of South Carolina Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 86)
    - University of Southern California Correspondence, 2012-2015 (Box 22, Folder 87)
    - Stanford Institute for Economics Policy Research Levin Points, 2013-2014 (Box 22, Folder 88)
    - Stevens Institute of Technology Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 89)
    - Tel Aviv University Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 90)
    - University of Texas Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 22, Folder 91)
    - Tianjin University Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 92)
    - University of Tokyo Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 93)
    - Tokyo Medical and Dental University Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 94)
    - Trinity College Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 95)
    - Tsing Hua College Correspondence, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 96)
    - Tsinghua University Correspondence, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 97)
    - Tsinghua University School of the Environment Collaboration, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 98)
    - Tulane University Certificate, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 99)
    - Turin School of Development Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 100)
    - University College London Call, 2014 April 14 (Box 22, Folder 101)
    - University College London Collaboration, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 102)
    - Vanderbilt University Cost of Regulating Compliance Overview, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 103)
    - University of Vermont Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 104)
    - University of Virginia Sexual Misconduct Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 105)
    - Waseda University Correspondence, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 106)
    - Western Connecticut State University Certificate, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 107)
    - Zhejiang University Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 22, Folder 108)
  - Professional Organizations
    - Alibaba Hong Kong Limited Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Annual Report, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - American Academy of Arts and Science Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - American Association of Independent Colleges and Universities - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - American Chemical Society Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Reports and Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - American Council of Trustees and Alumni Correspondence, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - American Council on Education Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - American Psychological Association Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Amistad Committee, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Anti-Defamation League - Tax Receipt and Correspondence, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Aramark Correspondence, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Ashoka Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Aspen Institute - Franklin Project, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Association for Psychological Science Correspondence, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Association of Academic Health Centers Correspondence, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Association of American Colleges and Universities Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Association of American Colleges and Universities Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Association of American Universities - Fall Membership Meeting, 2013 October 20 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Association of American Universities - Fall Membership Meeting, 2014 October 19 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Association of American Universities - Membership Meeting, 2014 April 27 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Association of American Universities - Memoranda, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Association of American Universities Profile Table, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Association of American Universities Stem Initiative, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Association of Governing Boards Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Association of Governing Boards Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Association of Literary Scholars, Critics and Writers Publication, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Association of Solving the Enigma for Peace on Earth Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - ATP Health Sciences Advisory Group Correspondence, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Barclay's Regulatory Requirements, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Boston Conservatory Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Peter B. Cannell and Co, Inc. Correspondence, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Center for Scientific Review - Award Extension Request, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Clifford Beers Clinic Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - College Survey Services Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Commission on Collegiate Nursing Education Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences Meeting, 2014 September 16 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Connecticut Campus Compact Meeting, 2013 September 13 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges - Directory, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges - Publishers Lunch, 2014 December 1 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Connecticut Health and Educational Facilities Authority, 2013-2014 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Consortium of Social Science Associations Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 2013 August 5 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education - Admission Statistics, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education - Alumni Survey, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education - Annual Meeting, 2010 December 10 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education - Annual Meeting, 2015 December 2 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education - Annual President's Meeting, 2014 December 3 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education Briefing, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education - Faculty Diversity, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education - Freshman Financial Aid and Admissions Survey, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education - Sources of Undergraduate Grant Aid, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education - Yellow Book Report, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Cortech Scientific Correspondence, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Council of Ivy League Presidents, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Council of Ivy League Presidents Agreement, 2015 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Council of Ivy League Presidents Concussion Data, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Council of Ivy League Presients - Ivy Manual, 2014-2015 (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Council of Ivy League Presidents - President's Meeting, 2013 December 10 (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - Professional Organziations - Council of Ivy League Presidents Meeting, 2014 June 11 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Council of Ivy League Presidents - President's Meeting, 2014 December 9 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Council of Ivy League Presidents Meeting, 2015 June 10 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Council of Ivy League Presidents - Publication, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Council on Education for Public Health - Accreditation Report, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Council on Education for Public Health - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Council on Education for Public Health - Visit, 2014 February 24 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Council on Foreign Relations Correspondence, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Council on Foreign Relations - Higher Education Working Group on Global Issues, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Dangote Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Data Haven Correspondence, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Fed Ex Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Four Havens Music Society Correspondence, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Fulbright Association Correspondence, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Gilead Sciences Visit, 2013 November 11 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Gilead Sciences Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Global Colloquium of University Presidents - Conference Call, 2013 September 13 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Global Colloquium of University Presidents - Doyle, 2014 September 11 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Global Colloquium of University Presidents Meeting, 2013 March 13 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Global Colloquium of University Presidents Meeting, 2014 February 12 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Global Colloquium of University Presidents - Summary Note, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Global Colloquium of University Presidents - Summary Report, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Global Health Corps Correspondence, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Global Human Resources Forum Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Global Institute of Environment and Sustainable Development - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Global University Leaders Forum - Call - 14 November, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Global University Leaders Forum (GULF) - meeting, 2015 January 22 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Globalization of Higher Education Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Greater New Haven Chamber of Commerce - Membership Directory, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Haskins Laboratories - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Higher Ed Jobs - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Human Rights Watch - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Hyundai Motor America - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Institute of International Education - Membership, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Institute of Medicine (folder 1 of 3), 2013 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Institute of Medicine (folder 2 of 3), 2013 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Institute of Medicine (folder 3 of 3), 2013 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Institute of Medicine Anonymous Donor, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Institute of Medicine - Salovey Article, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Institute of Medicine of the National Academies - Ballot, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Institute of Medicine of the National Academies - Member Booklet, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Institute of Medicine - New Member Material, 2013-2014 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Inter-Collegiate Athletic Consulting - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - International Alliance of Research Universities (IARU) Campus Sustainability Strategy, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - International Alliance of Research Universities (IARU) Meeting, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - International Alliance of Research Universities - National University of Singapore - Photographs, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - International Alliance of Research Universities - Notes, c. 2013 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - International Alliance of Research Universities - President's Meeting, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - International Alliance of Research Universities - President's Meeting (folder 1 of 2), 2015 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - International Alliance of Research Universities - President's Meeting (folder 2 of 2), 2015 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - ITHAKA - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Ivy Plus - Corporate and Foundation Relations Conference, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Jackson Laboratory - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Jewish Museum and Tolerance Center - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - JP Morgan Chase - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Johnson and Johnson Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Kirkland and Ellis - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Korea International Education Limited - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Leadership Alliance Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Leadership Alliance Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Leeway Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Maryland Higher Education Commission - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - MC2 Technology - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Minority Access - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - ML Strategies - Correspondence, 2013-2015 (Box 24, Folder 65)
    - Modern Language Association - Report, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 66)
    - Napier Initiative Correspondence, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 67)
    - National Academies Corrrespondence, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 68)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Correspondence, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 69)
    - National Academy of Sciences Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 70)
    - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities Correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 24, Folder 71)
    - National Association of Schools of Music - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 73)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association - Concussion Article, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 74)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 75)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association - Graduation Rates, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 76)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association - Report, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 77)
    - National Collegiate Hispanic Honor Society - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 78)
    - National Commission on Social, Emotional and Academic Development Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 79)
    - National Consortium for Building Healthy Academic Communities - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 80)
    - Pressional Organizations - National Council on the Humanities - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 81)
    - National Economic Council - Auguste Notes, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 82)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 83)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 84)
    - National Endowment for the Arts and National Endowment for the Humanities - Battleground, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 85)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Chamber of Commerce - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 86)
    - National Institutes of Health and National Science Foundation - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges, 2013-2014 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges - Accreditation, 2013-2015 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges - Five Year Interim Report, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges - Meeting, 2013 September 2-2013 September 3 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges - Membership Roster, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges - Mid-term Report, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges - Proposed Policy Changes, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - New England Development Research Association - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - New York Academy of Sciences Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - New York Academy of Sciences - Meeting, 2013 August 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - New York City Bar Association - Committee on International Human Rights, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Human Rights Watch - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Northeast Corridor Education Innovation Council, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - ONE Campaign - President Elliot Meeting, 2013 November 13 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Orchid Alliance Project - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Peta 2- Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Policy Sciences Center - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Poly Culture Group - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Post-Crisis World - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Prep for Prep - Annual Report, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Pricewaterhouse Coopers - Meeting, 2014 August 13 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Privatized Development for Public Sector - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Registry for College and University Presidents - Correspondence and Card, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - rEVO Biologies, Inc. - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - SAGE - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Sallie Mae - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Santander - Correspondence, 2012 -2014 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Santander - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Science Philanthropy Alliance - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Sciences Po - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Seaver Institute - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Significant Federation - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Smithsonian Institution - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Society of Behavioral Medicine - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Sony - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Sovereign Bank, 2013 February 6 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Strategy Matters, 2013-2014 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - TATA - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Thompson Reuters Corporation - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - UBI Index - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - United Nations Economic and Social Council - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Universia International Presidents Meeting - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Universities Research Association - Meeting, 2013 January 23 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - US News and World Report - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Mary Wade - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Washington Center for Internships and Academic Seminars - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Wellspring Advisors, LLC - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Wills Eye Hospital - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Witness for Peace New England - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Women's Health and Education Center - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Wonder Work - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - World Economic Forum - Annual Meeting Programme, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - World Economic Forum - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - World Economic Forum Academy - Overview, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - World Economic Forum - Global University Leaders Forum (GULF) - Meeting - 20 January (1 of 3), 2015 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - World Economic Forum - Global University Leaders Forum (GULF) - Meeting - 20 January (2 of 3), 2015 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - World Economic Forum - Global Univesity Leaders Forum (GULF) - Meeting - 20 January (3 of 3), 2015 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Residential Colleges
    - Berkeley College - Master Chun - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Calhoun College - Announcement, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Calhoun College - Master Appointment - Adams, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Calhoun College - Master Search - Announcement, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Calhoun College - Reunion, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Construction Costs - Memorandum, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Davenport College - Fellows, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Drawings by Cooper - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - Timothy Dwight College - Dean Mahurin - Announcement, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - Timothy Dwight College - Dean Resignation - Loge, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Timothy Dwight College - Master Appointment - Liu, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Timothy Dwight College - Master Resignation - Brenzel, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - Timothy Dwight College - Master Search - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - Jonathan Edwards College - Master Appointment - Laurans, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - Jonathan Edwards College - Master Laurans - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 74)
    - Jonathan Edwards College - Master Review, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 75)